How many tasks was assigned to Xiaohei?
Three
Why do you need to complete them?
After they are compelted, I'll become an executor!
I'll be qualified to become master's sidekick!
Oh......
What is an executor?
They are law enforcers
Ah, isn't that dangerous?
Mhm, that's why they go through tasks and examinations
isn't that the 2nd task too easy?
Maybe ti's for Xiaohei to get in close contact with humans
and learn to manage all kinds of situations
Ohhh~~
The time's up, we can open task 3
What's writte on it?
Earn the compliments of the elfin-king Folan, complete before New Year's Eve
Ah...... that's a lot of months
Folan......I've never heard of them......
That means we will have to find someone named Folan
and make him compliment you?
Eh......that's a rather strange task
Maybe they are in need of our help
Elfin King......Folan......
Who are the ones with that title?
Elfin King is a title among the elfin realm
Most famous among them, are probably Wukong and Nezha
That's due to them being included in many novels
Ohhh!
Nezha is an Elfin King?
Xiaohei, do you recognize him?
Mhm
Whoa!!~
Then what's the difference between an Elfin King and a god?
Elfin King usually refers to an elfin who have conquered a territory
No one's been given that title in a long time
So that's why master never mentioned it
and Nezha have already been bestowed the title of god
that's why it's never mentioned he's oncce an Elfin King
Does that mean, maybe FOlan isn't an Elfin King anymore either
Mhm, maybe we'll have to llok around for clues
No results online either
I'll ask around on elfin forums
The deadline is New Year's Eve, we have quite a bit of time
Let's wait for more info, look around tomorrow morning
Mhm, alright
Uh......
Who's even called that nowadays?
I can tell you very responsibly, no one
I know all the 87 recorded Elfin Kings in history,--------
none of them are named Folan
No one seems to know......
I'll leave the thread up, I'll look around for a bit
Shouldn't we ask someone?
those who know stuff like this, are probably older folks
Laojun must know!
Em......
no reason to bother him
Oh~~
Boring, none of the new shows are any good~ Why's no one visiting me~~
Diting~~Diting~~Diting~
Hush, I'm reading
hmph!
Elfin King Folan?
Uh, never heard of it
Old men like me have seen many things
But I really have never heard of someone with tha name
For Elfin Kings are quite different from hidden saints
Most of them are given that title for their famed and renowned power
That's why I think there doesn't exist such a formidible force within the mainland
What you're saying is, he might be an elfin King that lived elsewhere?
I'm not sure, but I can assure you we've never had one with that name
Mhm, alright, thank you kindly master
How as it?
Said there's no one named that in mainland
Maybe this is a task for abrod?
There are elfin abroad as well?
Haha, of course
As long it's a place creatures exists, elfins exist
That's why every nation have its own myths and legends
Then are they all among the crowd now?
Mhm, most of the elfins here abide by the law
What about elsewhere?
Currently coexistence is mainstream
But there are also nations ruled by elfins
They often only seek representatives among humans
citizens also treat them as their faith
Most of the other nations have treated them as fiction,
to lessen their impact
Humans now are committed to technology
and walks on a different path from Elfins
Which path is the correct one?
There's no absolute right answer
Humans, Elfins
compared to the world, is minuscule
They both have their limitations, and too many variables
Oooh~
What do we do next?
Is it against the rules to ask the guild?
Does it?
Who are you asking......
Then why don't we ask?
Uh......
Shanxin's call
What's up? Is everything tidied up?
If you're finished I'll come visit you guys~~
Apologies Shanxin
We might be away for a long while
We're on our way to complete a big mission
What mission?
Can I say it?
Can we?
Why are you asking me......
We might be out of the country, to look for an elfin
Oh? To which country?
Not sure, we don't know where he's at
That's why we are researching
Oooh
It's an Elfin King named Folan, do you know who he is?
How oculd Shanxin possibly know
Folan...
Is it a compliment from the Elfin King Folan?
HOW DO YOU KNOW?????
A game mission is the All Linving Creatures???
Yeah, this morning the game posted about 100 missions
Everyone's talking about it
Why didn't I find any search results from before?
This mission was updated 10 minutes ago
I just found out as well
There's a lot of replies from the thread now too......
So Xiaohei's 3rd mission......
Is an......In-Game Mission?
That simple?
Simple? Wrong
This is an impossible mission!
Haaah?
This means your final task is completing a video game?
Mhm
So what exactly is this mission about?
Earlier today the game published about 100 new missions
"Elfin King Folan's Compliments" is the last one posted
Human players that have reached level 200
[No Red Names]----------------
Hunt red name players from lv 60-200,-----------
every level with 2 claims
Complete all high level side quests
Acquire all artifacts------
and the hardest mission here
Hunt red name players from lv 60-200
every level with 2 claims
This seems liek a list of things by itself......
Completing this mission seems like one of the highest accomplishment within the game
There may not be a set limit to how players can complete it
but due its difficulty, I imagine there won't be many who can complete it
Seems like...collecting the artifacts is the easiest part?
Not quite.
Althought there are already player who've gotten artifacts,
but accordingto what's recorded online, there are only 11 types discovered thus far
There are 2 types left to be discovered
That means, over a couple 10s of millions of player have yet to complete a set of these artifacts
However, thinks like artifacts will only become more common as time goes on
There's gotta be those who obtained them but didn't wanna share it online
I figure after a couple days there will be detailed descriptions of all artifacts
So ar it seems, the hardest, is the first requirement
Isn't there players who are already level 50?
there's already those over level 100......
Since the game is quite special, there's been high level players since the server opened
So far out the players who are over level 60, Human players make up 12% of them
but they are all red-named
Not a single one without a red name
Others are all players of animals or mystical creatures
Mystical creatures starts with high base stats
People online have found that a lvl 1 mystical creature is the equivalent to a level 20-30 human
So currently most of the high level players high level players are mystical creatures
So currently most of the high level players are mystical creatures
but everyone seems to think human players will scale into stronger creatures later on
In short, reaching lvl 200 in itself is very difficult
and you also can't be red-named, which is even more difficult
Which part do you not understant, Xiaohei?
Everything......what's "astonishing" (Experience)...what's......
Ah that, let me explain
Ooooooh
I understand now!
If it's a normal game,
spending some time will ensure you reaching high levels
But in this game, if your character dies, they are gone
So to weaker players, it's possible to be level 1 forever
The hard part about this mission is that you cannot die before its completion
What's wrong Xiaohei?
These missions, maybe they are what executors must accomplish
So, is this the test of master Wuxian?
but you can only accept the mission once, can't do it again after you die
right, once ap erson dies of course the task is failed.....
We all die so quickly every time, isn't this a bit too hard?
Do you remember the transformation we saw yesterday?
That's a level 60 ability, called "Wild Form"
It allows beasts to attain a human form
Human players on the other hand can choose their Wild Shapes
So yesterday we must have been killed by a level 60 player
Xiaohei held up for quite a bit, we were all level 1!
So I belive we might be stronger than we think
We can try and test leveling up first
Once we get a bigger picture, we can return to lvl 1 to accept this mission
I wanna acept it right now
Since we already know the mission, we can't just have "test it out" as our attitude
We can't die, we must complete the mission in on go
thinking there's always next time, is wrong to begin with
Mhm
Fine with me!
In short, we can get killed, but Xiaohei must stay alive
Uh...doesn't sound that right
No one will die!
Mhm!
Then let's set the goal, all of us must stay alive
Mhm
Since we are going for it on our first try,
then let's prepare ourselves starting with the character creation
With the limited edition in hand, we have a lot of options
Let's be careful with every step from now on
The strongest one here is Xiaohei, we'll be relying on you in combat
I'll do my best to protect everyone
Combat and fighting, me and Xiaohei will handle it
Mhm, then I'll be the adviser
Then I am......
Gaming Xiaobai! [TL note: also slang for Novice]
Sprint abilities in the game is the same as real life, with 6 different categories
Beside spirit powers, it also test physical fitness and reaction
Ooh~
Shanxin for example, have great decision making and reaction speed
Perhaps it's due to the many games you've plated, have some good combat sense
But the body might not be able to keep up
Can try a summoning conjurer
You might be better suited for control
Are there any healing classes?
Yup, part of the living spirits branch, mainly for support
Em, I'll think about it, I'll decide once we get into the game
Let's keep it simple for Xiaobai, pick one from protective spirits branch
Mhm-Alright
Me and Xiaohei will stick with what we are good at
Hahaha, seems like the real deal!!
The current 4 tasks in the mission, the 2nd one seems impossible for now
We won't be callenging it for now
Let's prioritize the first taks
The 3rd and 4th can be completed while we level up
The focus here are the failure conditions
Death leads to failure, that much is obvious
Other than that. Task 2, 3 and 4 doesn't have any other losing conditions
We can complete them slowly
Mainly it's the 1st task, requiring no red-names
That means, if our names turn red, the mission is failed
This is quite dangerous
Because human characters spawns in their respective factions
for a realistic experience, there's no way for players to checck which faction others belong to
Even if they traverse to other territories they might encounter players from the same factions
That's why there are so many red-named players
Then what do we do?
I have an idea
We create our own faction!
Oh?
We create our own faction
this way, everyone else will be an enemy faction
As long as we don't kill each other, we won't be red-named
It's that easy?
Not quite, there are requirements for creating a faction
1. Creating a faction takes at least 3 players
2. Acquiring a faction territory
As soon as it's lost, the faction is disbanded
Good thing that hijacking faction grounds is part of a side quest
It's something we'll have to go through
How does hijacking work?
Destroy enemy faction leader! Replacint at once!
But faction members have a 4x power multiplier in their territory
Whoa......
There's already a world map made by some folks online
These colors are player territories
The greens are unclaimed wild grounds
Places like these require defeating bosses that spaws there to become factions grounds
Of course we know bosses are players as well
So it's the same thing as hijacking another faction's territory
But bosses have systematic buffs
Normal players need to group up in large numbers to defeat them
Bosses are an unknown to us
I've heard some are ridiculously powerful
Let's try hijacking another territory instead
If we can confirm a target,
I'm quite adept at assasinations
Eh?
Alright!
Let's begin!
Shanxin, you'll have to lay down to play~
Ugh, this episode is so boring
Whoa, seems like a desert this time
Xiaohei......
Did you hair turn black?
Mhm, it lets you choose the colors
Oh~~
Tha'ts adorable
Hahahahaha~
Alright, seems like we've made our group
Let's all accept this quest
Ok, this way the quest progression will auto-update
Right now our mission is to level up, then hijack a faction territory
but have to make sure we don't get red-named
Let's not deal with human players before forming a faction
Let's stick with non-human players for now to level safely
Mhm!
There's a lizard there
Do we get XP by killing it?
Let's not understimate any players
Mmmhm...
Oh?
What's wrong?
This place suddenly became private territory
Does that mean......someone defeated the boss that spawned here?
Success!
Whoa! You can see every player in our territory
ALRIGHT! Everyone split up, let's take them all!
OOOH--
Huh
Let's go for these
4 people
Oh, alright
Let's test out the faction territory buffs!!
ONWARDS! HAHAHAHA
Will this game ever have something like a transport tool?
Maybe in the future
How about it?
We should be out of here in 2 kilometers
Running doesn't seem tiring in this game
Oh?
They are all level 1s
Can't really fell the buff like this
Then let's quickly clear 'em, and look for the next group
Xiahei, can you take them?
Can't we kill other humans yet?
They must be a new faction, don't worry, it won't read-name ya
If you kill them, they won't actually die right
They are all substitutes, their true forms are unscathed
Didn't we "die" a couple times before
Mhm, understood
Dant it! What's going on!?
Whoa!!! Xiaohei is amazing!!!
Oh, we've leveled up
We're at Lv 11!
That means, the two we just defeated were Lv 28 or higher
Oh! We've unlocked Level Vision
Wink with 1 eye
We can see our levels!
Everyone's level 11
That went quite smoothly
I didn't think XIaohei was this much stronger than big bro
My physical traits are sub par, can't control spirits that well either
Xiaohei, how many of those enemies can you take?
As long they don't use anything unforseen, I can take all of them
Whoa......
That was Lv1 against Lv28
You've also leveled up mid-combat, aren't you invincible?
The quest doesn't seem so hard now
Ignoring level differences, attacking weak spots still cause death
This setting is definitely good for Xiaohei
But there are still many abilities we have to watch out for
They were clearly caugh off guard
Let's still be careful about it
Mmmhm
Let's distribute our attribute points
Mhm
This is the Spatial branch
What else does XIaohei use?
Mmmmm......
Add some to Iron elements in the defense branch
Then click here
Is it like this...and this?
Yup, Xiaohei is qute smart!
I can't really read, not really smart......
I can teach you to read!
Alright!
But I'm scared that I might not learn......
How come?
What now?
What do we do?
Let's run!
What! They were taken out?!
Go!
That's not good......there's too many
Even if Xiaohei can deal with them, some of us might die
Xiaohei! Look behind the group!
The last 4 people have the highest level, the faction leader must be one of 'em
If you can take them out,
We'll level up to uabout 20 and get the territorial buff
Alright
I seem to be stronger than before
Leave the rest to me!
Mhm!
Alright! The buff is ours!!
Now, they are invaders
We are level 25
Whoa......
Seems like we have quite the early advantage
They all have spiritual powers, but can't utilize it
THe changes in gameplay, even a pro-gamer like me can't adapt that well
But I don't think It'll take long,
before many becomes comfortable with this game
You sure this is a human?
Mhm, already confirmed with them
Interesting, this game is quite fun indeed
You sure you wanna kill kim?
Mhm, let's go
Speaking of, what abilities did Xiaobai pick?
Fire~~
Oh? that's unexpected
Fire is quite hard to control, why did you pick fire?
Because......
COOL!
But why can't I make even sparks, even though we are level 25......
There's not tutorial either
This is due to your control of Spiritual Power
despite its difficulty being lower than the real world
let me teach ya how to use it
What about you big bro, you are also Level 25, how'ts it compared to before?
Whoa~~
I think we might just be invincible
Now we have our own faction territory
Most players choose to grind levels in their own territory
but we of course must leave
To deal with players who leaves immediately after esablishing a faction
After others who enter this territory can receive quests to hunt down faction leaders
They'll receive their location on the map
Then let me be the faction leader,
no need for Xiaohei to take that role, or else he'll be followed
Mhm
This kind of quest can only be taken by humans
So any human that approach us could be suspicious
Understood
Are there really 10s of millions of players playing
Fells like there aren't many players around
Didn't we spawn into a populated central area last time
It might distribute players based on territory
The only permanent stat in this game is Map Progression
Spawn points are auomatically unlocked
Every respawn will be at different locations,
but take look at our progression percentage
Holy!
Even though this is a gmae from Elfins,
but how did they make it?
This might be someone's Spirit Realm
Eh?
Mhm
This body might be a replica, but it also really exists
Eh?
Wait
Are all of them players?
Won't they fight one another?
Maybe wolves are set to be unable to kill its own kind
What were you saying about no players?
Let's not complain for now......
AAAAWOOOOOO~~
Do we fight?
We can't take that many
Do we run?
We can't outrun 4 legs
THEN WHAT DO WE DO!!!!
Xiaohei run aay quickly!
DON'T GIVE UP SO EASILY!!
This is quite fun
This game's only been online for 3 days
How many humans like these do you think are there?
I'm looking forward to it
Stay with me aruite yukou ishikoro wo kette
Stay with me - let's walk on, kicking pebbles as we go
Yukisaki wa kitto kimagure demo
Our destination may be whimsical
Hana no kaori wo ryoute ni
But with the scent of flowers in both hands
kore kara deau kimi e to
I’ll carry it to the you I’ve yet to meet
Wait for me hanashi wo shiyou kata wo narabete
Wait for me — let’s talk, side by side
Hajimemashite wa gikochinaku temo
Even if our first “hello” is a little awkward
Mochiyotta hako aketara
When we open the boxes we’ve brought
Tsumekon da yume wo wakeaou
Let’s share the dreams we’ve packed inside
Mata ashita tte atarimae ni kawaseru hibi ga
The days when we can casually say “See you tomorrow”
Itoshikute hakanasugite
Are so precious and so fleeting
Omoi wa kitto kienai
Those feelings will never fade away
Sora wo nagareru kumo ni wa oitsukenai kedo
We can’t catch up to the clouds drifting across the sky
Ame ni natte hana wo tsukete kitto boku wo yonderu
But they’ll turn to rain, bloom into flowers
Kitto boku wo yonderu
And surely, they’re calling out to me